[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the symbol for Platinum?", "correct_answer": "Pt", "incorrect_answers": ["Pl", "P", "Pa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What wars did Star Wars character Obi Wan Kenobi fight in?", "correct_answer": "Clone Wars", "incorrect_answers": ["Rebellion Uprising", "Cold Wars", "Imperial Wars"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For what part of his anatomy was Jimmy Durante famous?", "correct_answer": "His large nose", "incorrect_answers": ["His large chin", "His large ears", "His large girth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "1931 saw the release of the first animated full length film with sound. In which country was it made?", "correct_answer": "Argentina", "incorrect_answers": ["The USA", "Germany", "Japan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What degree did actor Dax Shepard receive from UCLA?", "correct_answer": "in anthropology", "incorrect_answers": ["in philosophy", "in history", "in sociology"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Until its replacement by the EMS scale, the Medvedev-Sponheuer-K\u00e1rn\u00edk scale was the most commonly applied scale in Europe, used to measure what?", "correct_answer": "Earthquake intensity", "incorrect_answers": ["Hurricane intensity", "Wind speed", "Ultraviolet radiation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor received the award for Best Actor in a Supporting Role at the 72nd Academy Awards 2000?", "correct_answer": "Michael Caine", "incorrect_answers": ["Michael Clarke Duncan", "Tom Cruise", "Jude Law"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "James Bond travels on what train, in From Russia With Love?", "correct_answer": "Orient Express", "incorrect_answers": ["Western Pacific", "Flying Scotsman", "Mallard"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On a Gap Jeans commercial in 2003, Madonna appeared together with which famous American rapper?", "correct_answer": "Missy Elliott", "incorrect_answers": ["Notorious B.I.G.", "Eminem", "2Pac"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which term means fear of being touched?", "correct_answer": "Aphenphosmphobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Apotemnophobia", "Anuptaphobia", "Antlophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What percentage of water is removed from milk to make evaporated milk?", "correct_answer": "60%", "incorrect_answers": ["40%", "70%", "50%"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does James Bond do with the submarine device at the end of the film For Your Eyes Only?", "correct_answer": "He throws it  away and lets it crush on the rocks.", "incorrect_answers": ["He sends it to London in the diplomatic luggage.", "He hands it over to the Soviet General", "He hides it inside the Greek monastery."]}]